<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="100">A member of RaD, a Doser faction.

Like many other Dosers, Rummy is utterly addicted to
Coral-based drugs, and in his perpetually addled state, he
has convinced himself that he is an invincible demi-god.

Even should reality intervene with a costly defeat, he
will forget about the setback entirely by the next day—
only death can dispel his notions of invincibility now.</text>
<text id="101">A guerilla leader of the Rubicon Liberation Front.

A blue-collar worker who was involved in the construction
of the Grid, he is now dedicated to establishing symbiosis
with the Coral and building a future for Rubicon free from
planetary closure, inspired by Father Dolmayan's ideals.

Able-bodied and eager, he is zealously dedicated to the
cause—but he is more at home in the construction yard
than the cockpit.</text>
<text id="102">Gun Six of the Redguns, the Balam Group's AC squad.

As a young boy, Red's life was forever changed when he
saw the news broadcasts of Commander Michigan's brutal
triumphs in the Jupiter War.

Red trained through blood, sweat and tears in order to
emulate his idol, supporting his impoverished siblings
all the while. When the Balam admission examination
finally came, he won his place in the Redguns at the
very moment he stood to attention to greet the squad.</text>
<text id="103">An independent mercenary who snuck onto Rubicon hoping
to get rich quick, taking advantage of the chaos brought
about by the extraplanetary corporations' forays.

Under Nosaac's "economic theory," the funds of others are
but extensions of his own resources. Thus he continues to
take on debt with no intention of repayment, as in his
eyes, the money was his anyway. This does have the benefit
of allowing him to buy the latest in corporate technology
as soon as it hits the market; he considers the power of
his AC an asset to his credit score.</text>
<text id="104">Sixth squad leader of the Vespers, the Arquebus Group's
augmented human squad.

Maeterlinck is a product of Generation Eight, which was
held to have advanced the process to the point of
rendering all previous generations obsolete, bringing
about a new age of augmentation.

Unfailingly loyal to Arquebus, she has a reliable track
record in the field, and her conduct during missions has
established her as a risk-averse problem-solver.</text>
<text id="105">A warrior of the Rubicon Liberation Front.

As an infant, Ziyi was taken to Rubicon by her parents—
who, tempted by the promise of riches from Coral mining,
sought to make an illegal entry to the planet.

Only Ziyi survived the crash landing. She came under the
guardianship of Uncle Flatwell of the Rubicon Liberation
Front, and the core of an AC was the young orphan's cradle
as she grew up to become a Coral Warrior.</text>
<text id="106">Seventh squad leader of the Vespers, the Arquebus Group's
augmented human squad.
Swinburne is a product of Generation Seven, the first
to receive experimental augmentation using Coral
substitution technology.

This granted him enhanced aptitude as a pilot without the
usual complications—but with no obvious indication of
either efficacy or potential side effects, Swinburne's
fears and doubts turned into an overpowering paranoia,
the final jewel to crown his odious personality.</text>
<text id="107">Gun Three of the Redguns, the Balam Group's AC squad.

A born con artist, no scheme was too underhanded for
Wu Huahai during his days as criminal mastermind, and
exploitation of others was a byword for opportunity.
However, his illicit Feng Shui Pharmacy operation was
a fatal overstep, imperiling the health of Balam's
economic sphere and leading to widespread disease.

It was Nile, now the deputy commander of the Redguns,
who ultimately shut Wu Huahai down.</text>
<text id="108">A warrior of the Rubicon Liberation Front.

Paramour and personal attendant to Dolmayan, Freddie
maintains an aloof distance from his fellow comrades.

An admirer of the inner world of Dolmayan's mind, he
entered the battlefield so that the father of the
Liberation Front would never need be alone.</text>
<text id="109">Fifth squad leader of the Vespers, the Arquebus Group's
augmented human squad.
Like Swinburne, Hawkins is a member of Generation Seven,
and has lost a great many colleagues and subordinates to
the progress of science in revolutionizing the surgery.

However, he has reached a certain peace with their
sacrifices, knowing that his generation of surgery is far
safer than those of the past—free of the loss of humanity
inflicted on the Coral technology generations, or the
grisly accidents of the interim generations.</text>
<text id="110">Gun Five of the Redguns, the Balam Group's AC squad.

A backstreet gambler, Iguazu bet big and lost, and he
was forced to undergo experimental 4th-generation
augmentation surgery to pay back his debtors.

In his new life, he quickly began to quarrel with Volta,
his oftentimes partner in crime. Iguazu's recalcitrant
nature was such that one day he even picked a fight with
the Hero of Jupiter, who retaliated with such fury that
Iguazu never quite looked the same afterward.</text>
<text id="111">A wandering independent mercenary who shelters with
the Rubicon Liberation Front.
Well versed in long-lost classical theater, he has a
particular interest in "ninjas" and "kabuki," relics of
the past that he learned of from the Japanese immigrant
culture which now heavily influences his eccentric style.

Once, when Rokumonsen was on the brink of starvation, he
was rescued by Ziyi, who offered him food and shelter—and
ever since that day, he has been the sworn enemy of those
who would do her and her comrades harm.</text>
<text id="112">Gun Four of the Redguns, the Balam Group's AC squad.

After beating the rebellious Volta and Iguazu into
submission, Michigan made it his personal crusade to make
something of the two, and thus began their daily hell.

For the past seven years, neither Volta nor Iguazu have
achieved their goal: "to punch the living daylights out
of Michigan, then get the hell out of the Redguns" (as
they would put it). Volta has since admitted defeat,
and is now learning about business from Wu Huahai.</text>
<text id="113">Eighth squad leader of the Vespers, the Arquebus Group's
augmented human squad.
A product of Generation Ten—the latest, and currently
practiced, form of augmentation surgery—Pater represents
the culmination of efforts to preserve the patient's
humanity through Coral replacement technology.

At times, his noticeably unreserved remarks hint at an
underlying lack of empathy—one might assume this to be
a side effect of the surgery, but this trait has in fact
been with him since long before his augmentation.</text>
<text id="114">A veteran independent mercenary who was active in the
star system surrounding Rubicon before the Fires of Ibis.
Sulla is a patient of Generation One augmentation—or
better said, a survivor, as the technology in its infancy
had less than a 10% success rate. Though he escaped the
fate of the others, Sulla is followed by the specter of
Death wherever he goes.

After receiving his surgery, Sulla lost interest in most
mercenary work, and now lives only for the hunt.
It is unclear who currently employs him.</text>
<text id="115">The right hand of RaD's ringleader and chief engineer,
"Cinder" Carla.

One day, Carla built a simple suggestion-based AI to
provide basic support and occasional entertainment.

However, no matter what conversational prompt she gave
"him," he would never say more than necessary.

Instead, it seemed that he was content to be a good
listener to his creator's free-spirited, eccentric ideas.</text>
<text id="116">The de facto military leader of the Rubicon Liberation
Front.

His authority is second only to that of Father Dolmayan,
and his standing within the organization has earned him
an informal title as a fellow elder—he is the "Uncle" of
the Liberation Front to Dolmayan's "Father."

For a time, Flatwell worked as a spy within the
extraplanetary corporations, and has sway over a rather
significant contact in Schneider's HR department.</text>
<text id="117">Third squad leader of the Vespers, the Arquebus Group's
augmented human squad.

O'Keeffe is originally a member of an older generation of
augmented humans, and during the Island Four Disturbance,
he worked as an agent carrying out espionage activities.

He was later headhunted by Arquebus's Information Dept.,
and agreed to sign up on the condition that they provided
him with Generation Nine augmentation surgery to
counteract the Coral burn-in on his brain.</text>
<text id="118">The ringleader of RaD and its chief engineer, responsible
for the basic specifications of all of the organization's
products.

A specialist in data processing and machine design, and
a fount of knowledge with an imaginative genius, "Cinder"
Carla has produced a long line of eccentric and fanciful
weaponry quite unlike those found in a corporate catalog.

Her stated design philosophy: "What use is a killing
machine that can't get a good laugh?"</text>
<text id="119">An independent mercenary who bargained his way into
an effortless entry to Rubicon, having anticipated the
extraplanetary corporations' forays well before they
made their move.

A specialist in corporate wetwork, Coldcall "removes"
undesirable elements on the behalf of those who do not
wish to be seen getting their hands dirty.

Quick to identify a fellow assassin, he claims that
"you can smell a real killer right through their AC."</text>
<text id="120">Fourth squad leader of the Vespers, the Arquebus Group's
augmented human squad.

Discovered through the recruitment program operated by
Schneider, an Arquebus affiliate, Rusty so quickly
distinguished himself that he was selected to join the
upper echelons of Vespers in less than half a year.

Rusty received augmentation surgery prior to joining the
Vespers, and though the precise details are unclear, he
has declared himself to be of the eighth generation.</text>
<text id="121">Leader of the Junker Coyotes, a major Doser force.

Brute was originally hired by RaD. His smooth-talking,
affable nature quickly caught the attention of Carla,
who found him quite unlike the average Doser.

When it was discovered that the man was a psychopath
and a pathological liar, he fled, taking a considerable
amount of RaD's funds and technology with him—a loss that
was too great for Carla to tolerate.</text>
<text id="122">Deputy commander of the Redguns, the Balam Group AC
squad. Formerly the commander of the Balam Security
Force, a paramilitary police organization that preceded
the formation of the Redguns.

Nile distinguished himself with an exceptionally high
arrest rate, and in those days, the only man he never
managed to put in handcuffs was Michigan, then the
commander of the rival Furlong Armed Fleet.
Having failed to arrest the man, he instead settled for
a friendly drink with his old nemesis.</text>
<text id="123">Deputy commander of the Vespers, the Arquebus Group's
augmented human squad.

After receiving Generation Eight augmentation surgery,
Snail continued to receive follow-up treatments as new
technologies entered the mainstream so as to make their
merits his own.

Many augmented humans have died in order to assure the
safety of his repeated "adjustments."</text>
<text id="124">An independent mercenary who arrived on Rubicon around
the time that the Coral response was rediscovered.

Held to be a member of Branch, a hacktivist collective
active in the Rubicon system, Chartreuse is said to have
dealt a critical blow to the Closure System during the
plot to attack Station 31.

Branch is made up of a rotating group of four people,
and Chartreuse is believed to be the second-oldest of
the current roster.</text>
<text id="125">Father of the Rubicon Liberation Front, veteran military
commander, and founder of the school of Coral mysticism.

As a young man, Dolmayan was once a Doser vagrant—
until the Fires of Ibis burned the star system.
In the Fires' aftermath, he developed an ardent belief
in symbiosis with the Coral.

This belief informed the founding ideals of the Rubicon
Liberation Front—ideals that have made martyrs of
countless Coral Warriors.</text>
<text id="126">An independent mercenary who arrived on Rubicon around
the time that the Coral response was rediscovered.

Held to be a member of Branch, a hacktivist collective
active in the Rubicon system, King is said to have
confounded an entire fleet of heavy warships in a solo
diversionary maneuver during the attack on Station 31.

Branch is made up of a rotating group of four people, and
King is believed to be the oldest of the current roster.</text>
<text id="127">Commander of the Redguns, the Balam Group's AC squad.
Michigan took up leadership after a career as the
commander of the Furlong Armed Fleet. There, he earned
a reputation as a merciless, heavy-handed ogre of a man,
and he was equally feared by friend and foe alike, who
knew him as "Hell on Four Legs."

Apparently, he has posted a bounty on his own head to
Balam's bounty board—with the stipulation that half
of the reward money is to be distributed among his
former comrades at Furlong.</text>
<text id="128">Commander of the Vespers, the Arquebus Group's augmented
human squad.

An ace pilot who achieved an astonishing 94.7% mission
success rate during the Island Four Disturbance, Freud
is widely suspected to be a recipient of repeated
"adjustments" much like Snail.

However, the real Freud is simply an ordinary human
being—a man who enjoys piloting his AC and making
incremental improvements on his daily sorties.</text>
<text id="200">Integration Program: Phase 1
----------------
As part of its mercenary support initiatives, ALLMIND
conducts its own research and development of AC parts.

This particular research exercise concerns the extension
of human sensory capabilities.

Through a process of continuous improvement, ALLMIND will
create an AC that, to the pilot, feels like an extension
of their own body.</text>
<text id="201">Integration Program: Phase 1
----------------
As part of its mercenary support initiatives, ALLMIND
also provides a beginner's program for new mercenaries.

Many mercenaries have benefited from the Trainer's
guidance and successfully flown from the nest.

ALLMIND monitors the progress of trainees in order to
further improve the program.</text>
<text id="202">Integration Program: Phase 1, Final Analysis
----------------
As part of its mercenary support initiatives, ALLMIND
also provides sample AC assemblies for beginners.

For pilots who are not augmented humans, it can be
extremely difficult to reassemble an entire AC and
immediately adapt to it.

ALLMIND strives to create a future where all mercenaries
can enjoy a near-symbiotic relationship with their ACs.</text>
<text id="203">Integration Program: Phase 2
----------------
Drawing from the evaluations thus far, ALLMIND has
updated the MIND ALPHA model.

The revised model features an AI that benefits from the
breadth of ALLMIND's research archives.

ALLMIND anticipates that this new model, MIND BETA, can
autonomously operate in actual combat at the same level
as a highly skilled mercenary.</text>
<text id="204">Integration Program: Phase 2
----------------
As part of its ongoing fundamental research, ALLMIND is
now analyzing the design concepts of the ACs employed by
the various factions on Rubicon.
By understanding these humanoid craft, we gain a greater
understanding of how their designers perceive humanity.

The extraplanetary corporations believe humanity to be
powerless against its environment; thus they maximize
the power of their ACs to subjugate their surroundings.</text>
<text id="205">Integration Program: Phase 2, Final Analysis
----------------
As part of its ongoing fundamental research, ALLMIND is
now analyzing the design concepts of the ACs employed by
the various factions on Rubicon.

The Rubiconian ACs are defined by a tendency to focus on
harmony with the human body in varying degrees. A sign,
perhaps, that they have embraced humanity's potential as
beings that exist within nature, and that they intend to
maximize this through optimization of human-driven input.</text>
<text id="206">Integration Program: Phase 3
----------------
Drawing from the evaluations thus far, ALLMIND has
updated the MIND BETA model.

This new MIND model is assembled from parts that have
been verified for high compatibility with the traits of
older generations of augmented humans.

ALLMIND kindly requests that you test the revised model
when opportunity allows.</text>
<text id="207">Integration Program: Phase 3
----------------
The Rubicon Research Institute was once the heart of
Coral research.

There, the Institute's scientists developed ACs that have
a distinct focus on the biological analogies between
humanity and Coral.

Their ACs enable the two to complement each other and
evolve in symbiotic harmony... A fascinating approach.</text>
<text id="208">Integration Program: Phase 3, Final Analysis
----------------
The independent mercenaries are the best representatives
of Core Theory put into practice.
Each and every operation of their ACs determines the odds
of their survival—and so they have no choice but to
perceive their ACs as extensions of their bodies.

Your partner for this evaluation will be a recreation of
a legendary independent mercenary who operates in the
shadows, reproduced from the little data available.</text>
<text id="209">AC data added to the Integration Program.
Encrypted and accompanied by a note.
----------------
...Elcano has stolen Arquebus technology and used it to
develop a new model. The fact that this craft has entered
the hands of the Rubicon Liberation Front is acceptable;
however, the time is not yet right.

We must wait for Arquebus to put the primary factor for
the Project in place.</text>
<text id="210">AC data added to the Integration Program.
Encrypted and accompanied by a note.
----------------
...The last of the Ibis series has made itself known.

We have identified a promising candidate to serve as the
Project's secondary factor—this machine must be destroyed
to remove any further obstructions.

That man has greatly delayed our efforts to put the third
factor in place... Revisions must be made.</text>
<text id="211">AC data that Ayre discovered in the Integration Program.
Appears to be a sample that ALLMIND was testing.
----------------
Raven. I was looking for a follow-up to MIND GAMMA,
but I couldn't find anything here...

I did find something else, though—a vast hoard of
prototypes built with Institute parts.

But there may be some way to put these to use...</text>
</entries>
</fmg>
