<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="70000000">First-generation FCS developed by Furlong Dynamics.
This model dates from a time before Furlong specialized
in missile development, but it remains in production due
to its balanced performance and low energy burden.</text>
<text id="70010000">Second-generation FCS developed by Furlong Dynamics.
This model was developed just as Furlong transitioned to
its specialization in missiles, and improves on the first
gen's specs while retaining its balanced performance.</text>
<text id="70010100">Second-generation FCS developed by Furlong Dynamics.
This model was developed after Furlong had established
itself as a true missile specialist, and is principally
designed to reduce missile lock time.</text>
<text id="70010200">Second-generation FCS developed by Furlong Dynamics.
This model was developed after Furlong had established
itself as a true missile specialist, and is principally
designed to improve multi-lock performance.</text>
<text id="70010300">Close-range combat FCS developed by Balam. In order to
achieve overwhelming superiority in close-range firearms
combat, Balam made compromises in missile performance
to instead focus on precise targeting assistance.</text>
<text id="70010400">FCS for assault operations developed by Balam. Taking
lessons from the Jupiter War, Balam improved the missile
performance of their FCS products, leading to the creation
of this long-seller with excellent overall balance.</text>
<text id="70020000">Long-range combat FCS designed by Arquebus ADD.
A concept model designed for obliterating targets well
before contact—in many respects, a move away from Core
Theory toward earlier visions of mechanized warfare.</text>
<text id="70020100">Long-range combat FCS designed by Arquebus ADD.
Retains ADD's earlier focus on obliterating targets at
range, while also improving missile performance across
the board to enable a "walking fortress" style of AC.</text>
<text id="70030000">FCS for unpiloted ACs, developed long ago by the Rubicon
Research Institute. Capable of exceptionally high-resolution
capture in close-range engagements, making no concessions
for the human brain's limitations in processing visuals.</text>
<text id="70030100">FCS for piloted ACs, developed long ago by the Rubicon
Research Institute. Adapted for Coral data conductors
while still faithful to Core Theory. Excellent processing
capabilities that virtually extend the pilot's senses.</text>
</entries>
</fmg>
