<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="65000000">Internal combustion generator developed by BAWS for
an old-generation AC. Performance is not dissimilar to
generic labor MT models, making it an unreliable choice
for combat use in a modern AC build.</text>
<text id="65010000">Internal combustion generator developed by Dafeng Core
Industries. Commissioned by Balam, the specifications for
this model demanded lightweight construction matched
with excellent EN recharge capabilities.</text>
<text id="65010100">Internal combustion generator developed by Dafeng Core
Industries. A joint development with Balam, this model
focuses on ensuring good EN capacity and recharging.</text>
<text id="65010200">Circulating-current generator developed by Arquebus.
Tailored to lightweight ACs, such as those built by
Schneider, efforts were made to keep its weight modest
while providing capable output for its size.</text>
<text id="65010300">Circulating-current generator developed by Arquebus.
The design goal for this model was to create a generator
with no drawbacks, resulting in a product that provides
stable performance in any AC assembly.</text>
<text id="65010400">Internal combustion generator developed by BAWS for modern
ACs. A balanced model capable of withstanding the demands
of modern combat, its development was aimed at narrowing
Rubicon's post-closure technological gap.</text>
<text id="65020000">Circulating-current generator designed by Arquebus ADD.
Engineered to support high-spec energy weapon prototypes,
it maximizes EN output at the expense of sacrificing
performance in other regards.</text>
<text id="65020100">Circulating-current generator designed by Arquebus ADD.
Engineered to maximize energy weapon specialization, this
model even sacrifices EN output to a degree, positioning
its performance somewhere close to a concept model.</text>
<text id="65030000">Coral-based internal combustion generator developed long
ago by the Rubicon Research Institute. This model takes
advantage of the Coral's biological traits, enabling rapid
recovery by pushing combustion to its limit.</text>
<text id="65030100">Prototype Coral-based internal combustion generator
developed long ago by the Rubicon Research Institute.
Optimized for power-hungry Coral weapons, with rapid
EN recovery enabled by maximized combustion.</text>
<text id="65040000">Internal combustion generator developed by Dafeng Core
Industries. This model was designed for use with the
corporation's independently-manufactured heavyweight
ACs, and features outstanding EN capacity.</text>
<text id="65040100">Circulating-current generator developed by Arquebus.
Designed with a focus on EN capacity and output to support
Arquebus energy weapons, it supplies more raw power than
any other corporate product on the market.</text>
<text id="65040200">BAWS internal combustion generator developed in tandem
with Elcano. Improved output allows for use of high-burden
parts, but supply recovery performance leaves much to be
desired, calling for a degree of EN management finesse.</text>
<text id="65040300">Circulating-current generator designed by Arquebus ADD.
Features improved EN capacity and output while retaining a
focus on energy weapon specialization. However, it suffers
from a heavy weight burden and recharging difficulties.</text>
</entries>
</fmg>
