<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="60000000">Second-generation booster developed by Furlong Dynamics.
Designed to counteract the inevitable weight increases
that result from improving AC performance. Performs well
in a variety of assemblies including medium-weight builds.</text>
<text id="60010000">Booster developed by RaD for heavy combat machines.
Extended Quick Boost jet duration allows for reliable
thrust regardless of weight. The eccentric model number
suggests development under intoxicating influences.</text>
<text id="60020000">Booster specialized for initial thrust, developed by
Schneider. Intended for use with Schneider frames,
it allows for extremely high evasive performance
when used as part of a lightweight assembly.</text>
<text id="60030000">Booster specialized for high mobility, developed by
Schneider. Commissioned by Arquebus, this part is
well balanced and offers stable performance even
when used as part of a medium-weight assembly.</text>
<text id="60040000">Booster specialized for long-distance cruising, developed
by Schneider. Maximizes Assault Boost thrust and energy
efficiency to provide excellent performance when rapidly
closing in on a target from long range.</text>
<text id="60050000">Second-generation booster developed by Furlong Dynamics.
This model prizes movement speed over Quick Boost
thrust, making it a good fit for assemblies that are
designed for endurance.</text>
<text id="60060000">Booster developed by RaD for lightweight machines.
A design subcontracted by Elcano, this model was built for
transport operations in the Grid and on other complex
terrain, with only a modest EN requirement when in midair.</text>
<text id="60070000">Prototype booster for piloted ACs, developed long ago by
the Rubicon Research Institute. This model's design
makes allowances for exoatmospheric operation, with a
particular focus on enhanced Quick Boost-related specs.</text>
<text id="60070100">Booster for unpiloted ACs, developed long ago by the
Rubicon Research Institute. No consideration has been
given to the g-force tolerance of human pilots, enabling
uncompromising performance and rapid-fire Quick Boosts.</text>
<text id="60070200">Booster developed by BAWS for an old-generation AC.
An early AC model, it marked an attempt to faithfully
represent Core Theory, and so its booster's specs were
tweaked for melee performance—such was the trend.</text>
<text id="60070300">Booster developed by RaD for heavyweight machines.
Designed for heavy-industry ACs primarily working on
the ground, it suffers from a slow vertical boost but
boasts excellent energy efficiency.</text>
<text id="60070400">First-generation booster developed by Furlong Dynamics.
Though inferior to current models, this booster remains
a viable choice, especially for lightweight assemblies,
due to its modest energy burden and ease of use.</text>
</entries>
</fmg>