<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="50000000">Medium-weight head part developed by Balam. The simple
design and solid performance of this model make it suited
for mass production—reflecting Balam's strategy of
overwhelming its enemies with its material superiority.</text>
<text id="50000100">Head part for a combat AC developed by RaD. Though it
was assembled from a patchwork of reclaimed resources,
RaD mobilized its entire engineering team to fine-tune
its design for formidable performance.</text>
<text id="50000200">Retrofitted head part developed by Balam. This high-end
model is a strong performer with a hefty energy footprint,
and features an intimidating spider-eye design chosen to
suit the tastes of the Redguns' commander.</text>
<text id="50000300">Custom head part developed by Balam. Altered to improve
combat suitability, the revisions to this model include
partial armor plating and the addition of a scanner
module.</text>
<text id="50010000">Head part developed by Dafeng Core Industries for the
heavyweight TIAN-QIANG AC. Incorporates only the most
essential functionality with a minimalist build in keeping
with Dafeng's "stout tree, slender branches" philosophy.</text>
<text id="50020000">Lightweight head part developed by Schneider.
Schneider is a specialist in aerodynamic research,
and this model reflects their experience with a light
but highly stable build.</text>
<text id="50020100">Expanded head part developed by Schneider.
This model further improves on stability but with
a higher energy burden, resulting in excellent
performance in aerial combat.</text>
<text id="50030000">Mass-produced head part developed by Arquebus.
A number of refinements and updates have been made to the
strong foundation laid by the preceding model, creating a
masterpiece in the realm of second-generation AC parts.</text>
<text id="50030100">Head part developed by Arquebus, derived from an existing
model. Engineered in anticipation of regular use by the
Vespers, this model features further improvements to
stability.</text>
<text id="50040000">Heavyweight head part designed by Arquebus ADD.
Incorporates cutting-edge technology to enable defiance of
the PCA. This model's distinctive curved armor plating
provides solid defense against damage of all kinds.</text>
<text id="50040100">Special head part designed by Arquebus ADD. Engineered to
accommodate a proposal from V.VII, this model maximizes
scanning performance, positioning its overall performance
close to that of a surveillance-oriented concept model.</text>
<text id="50050000">Head part developed by ALLMIND for model ACs. Designed
as part of a research project to extend human sensory
capabilities, with numerous optimizations to create an AC
that, to the pilot, feels like an extension of the body.</text>
<text id="50050100">Model head part developed by ALLMIND.
In line with a change in approach, this part maximizes
stability at the expense of armor robustness.</text>
<text id="50060000">Lightweight head part developed by Elcano. In keeping
with Elcano's roots in producing and forging steel, this
model exhibits craftsman-like flair, being light while
providing reliable defenses.</text>
<text id="50070200">Head part developed by BAWS for an old-generation AC.
Said AC was one of the earliest models, developed to
succeed MT-class machines, and modern fans of such
classic hardware are fond of its characteristic bulk.</text>
<text id="50070300">Head part for construction ACs developed by RaD.
Specced for demolition work, this model makes up for
combat performance shortcomings with its sturdiness
and outstanding defensive performance.</text>
<text id="50070400">Head part for scout ACs developed by RaD. Originally
specced for surveying terrain, this model makes up for
what it lacks in combat performance with a light energy
footprint and commendable ease of use.</text>
<text id="50070600">Custom part derived from the scout AC head developed by
RaD. Comprehensively rebuilt for combat by an anonymous
independent mercenary group, this model takes some steps
forward but sacrifices the minimalism of its predecessor.</text>
<text id="50080000">Head part for the HAL 826 piloted AC, developed long ago
by the Rubicon Research Institute. The last of the Ibis
Series and the only piloted Ibis craft, it was built to be
the final safety valve to prevent a Coral Collapse.</text>
<text id="50080100">Head part for the EPHEMERA unpiloted ACs, developed long
ago by the Rubicon Research Institute. An old development
quirk allows for piloted operation, but one should not
expect any concessions for the limits of human sight.</text>
<text id="50080200">A new head part developed by Elcano. This model utilizes
technology received from Furlong Dynamics to achieve
improved overall balance and precise AC control.</text>
<text id="50900000">Junk. Originally a head part for an old-generation AC
developed by BAWS. RaD engineers infiltrated Institute
City to make field repairs—just enough to make this part
operable, but not enough to fix its weathered armor.</text>
<text id="51000000">Medium-weight core part developed by Balam. The simple
design and solid performance of this model make it suited
for mass production—reflecting Balam's strategy of
overwhelming its enemies with its material superiority.</text>
<text id="51000100">Core part for a combat AC developed by RaD. Though it
was assembled from a patchwork of reclaimed resources,
RaD mobilized its entire engineering team to fine-tune
its design for formidable performance.</text>
<text id="51000300">Custom core part developed by Balam. Altered to improve
combat suitability, this model features a lighter basic
frame enhanced with partial armor plating to maintain a
modest weight.</text>
<text id="51010000">Core part developed by Dafeng Core Industries for the
heavyweight TIAN-QIANG AC. This is the "trunk" in Dafeng's
"stout tree, slender branches" philosophy; a defensive
foundation with extremely heavy, sturdy armor.</text>
<text id="51020000">Lightweight core part developed by Schneider.
Schneider is a specialist in aerodynamic research,
and this model reflects their experience with a light
and highly agile build.</text>
<text id="51030000">Mass-produced core part developed by Arquebus.
A number of refinements and updates have been made to the
strong foundation laid by the preceding model, creating a
masterpiece in the realm of second-generation AC parts.</text>
<text id="51040000">Heavyweight core part designed by Arquebus ADD.
Incorporates cutting-edge technology to enable defiance of
the PCA. This model features excellent generator output
adjustment and solid defense against damage of all kinds.</text>
<text id="51050000">Core part developed by ALLMIND for model ACs. Designed
as part of a research project to extend human sensory
capabilities, with numerous optimizations to create an AC
that, to the pilot, feels like an extension of the body.</text>
<text id="51060000">Lightweight core part developed by Elcano. In keeping
with Elcano's roots in producing and forging steel, this
model exhibits craftsman-like flair, being light while
providing reliable defenses.</text>
<text id="51070200">Core part developed by BAWS for an old-generation AC.
Said AC was one of the earliest models, developed to
succeed MT-class machines, and modern fans of such
classic hardware are fond of its characteristic bulk.</text>
<text id="51070300">Core part for construction ACs developed by RaD.
Specced for demolition work, this model makes up for
combat performance shortcomings with its sturdiness
and outstanding physical defenses.</text>
<text id="51070400">Core part for scout ACs developed by RaD. Originally
specced for extravehicular activity in space, this model
makes up for what it lacks in combat performance with
a light energy footprint and commendable ease of use.</text>
<text id="51080000">Core part for the HAL 826 piloted AC, developed long ago
by the Rubicon Research Institute. The last of the Ibis
Series and the only piloted Ibis craft, it was built to be
the final safety valve to prevent a Coral Collapse.</text>
<text id="51080100">Core part for the EPHEMERA unpiloted ACs, developed long
ago by the Rubicon Research Institute. An old development
quirk allows for piloted operation, but the core box makes
only perfunctory concessions for a human occupant.</text>
<text id="51080200">A new core part developed by Elcano. This model utilizes
technological insights derived from analyzing Schneider
ACs to achieve improved overall balance and high
suitability for aerial combat.</text>
<text id="51900000">Junk. Originally a core part for an old-generation AC
developed by BAWS. RaD engineers infiltrated Institute
City to make field repairs—just enough to make this part
operable, but not enough to fix its weathered armor.</text>
<text id="52000000">Medium-weight arm parts developed by Balam. The simple
design and solid performance of this model make it suited
for mass production—reflecting Balam's strategy of
overwhelming its enemies with its material superiority.</text>
<text id="52000100">Arm parts for a combat AC developed by RaD. Though it
was assembled from a patchwork of reclaimed resources,
RaD mobilized its entire engineering team to fine-tune
its design for formidable performance.</text>
<text id="52000300">Custom arm parts developed by Balam. Altered to improve
combat suitability, this model features a lighter basic
frame while also enhancing arm maneuverability.</text>
<text id="52010000">Arm parts developed by Dafeng Core Industries for the
heavyweight TIAN-QIANG AC. Built to embody Dafeng's
"stout tree, slender branches" philosophy, their weight
is balanced by heavy upper arms and lighter forearms.</text>
<text id="52010100">Revised arm parts developed by Dafeng Core Industries.
This model attempts to further refine Dafeng's "stout
tree, slender branches" philosophy by enhancing the
durability of the armor plating around the shoulders.</text>
<text id="52020000">Lightweight arm parts developed by Schneider.
Schneider is a specialist in aerodynamic research,
and this model reflects their experience with a light
and highly agile build.</text>
<text id="52030000">Mass-produced arm parts developed by Arquebus.
A number of refinements and updates have been made to the
strong foundation laid by the preceding model, creating a
masterpiece in the realm of second-generation AC parts.</text>
<text id="52030100">Arm parts developed by Arquebus, derived from an existing
model. Engineered in anticipation of regular use by the
Vespers, this model features further improvements to
performance.</text>
<text id="52040000">Heavyweight arm parts designed by Arquebus ADD.
Incorporates cutting-edge technology to enable defiance of
the PCA. This model's distinctive curved armor plating
provides solid defense against damage of all kinds.</text>
<text id="52050000">Arm parts developed by ALLMIND for model ACs. Designed
as part of a research project to extend human sensory
capabilities, with numerous optimizations to create an AC
that, to the pilot, feels like an extension of the body.</text>
<text id="52060000">Lightweight arm parts developed by Elcano. In keeping
with Elcano's roots in producing and forging steel, this
model exhibits craftsman-like flair, being light while
providing dependable carrying capacity.</text>
<text id="52070200">Arm parts developed by BAWS for an old-generation AC.
Said AC was one of the earliest models, developed to
succeed MT-class machines, and modern fans of such
classic hardware are fond of its characteristic bulk.</text>
<text id="52070300">Arm parts for construction ACs developed by RaD.
Specced for demolition work, this model makes up for
combat performance shortcomings with its sturdiness
and excellent recoil control.</text>
<text id="52070400">Arm parts for scout ACs developed by RaD. Originally
specced for recovering scrap, this model makes up for
what it lacks in combat performance with a light energy
footprint and commendable ease of use.</text>
<text id="52080000">Arm parts for the HAL 826 piloted AC, developed long ago
by the Rubicon Research Institute. The last of the Ibis
Series and the only piloted Ibis craft, it was built to be
the final safety valve to prevent a Coral Collapse.</text>
<text id="52080100">Arm parts for the EPHEMERA unpiloted ACs, developed long
ago by the Rubicon Research Institute. An old development
quirk allows for piloted operation, albeit with actuation
translation that outstrips the capability of human nerves.</text>
<text id="52080200">New arm parts developed by Elcano. This model utilizes
technology received from Furlong Dynamics to achieve
improved overall balance and precise AC control.</text>
<text id="52900000">Junk. Originally arm parts for an old-generation AC
developed by BAWS. RaD engineers infiltrated Institute
City to make field repairs—just enough to make this part
operable, but not enough to fix its weathered armor.</text>
<text id="53000000">Medium-weight bipedal leg parts developed by Balam. The
simple design and solid performance of this model make it
suited for mass production—reflecting Balam's strategy
of overwhelming its enemies with its material superiority.</text>
<text id="53000100">Bipedal leg parts for a combat AC developed by RaD.
Though it was assembled from a patchwork of reclaimed
resources, RaD mobilized its entire engineering team to
fine-tune its design for formidable performance.</text>
<text id="53000300">Custom bipedal leg parts developed by Balam. Altered to
improve combat suitability, this model features a lighter
basic frame enhanced with partial armor plating to
maintain a modest weight.</text>
<text id="53010000">Bipedal legs developed by Dafeng Core Industries for the
heavyweight TIAN-QIANG AC. Built to embody Dafeng's
"stout tree, slender branches" philosophy, their weight
is balanced by heavy upper legs and lighter lower legs.</text>
<text id="53020000">Lightweight bipedal leg parts developed by Schneider.
Schneider is a specialist in aerodynamic research,
and this model reflects their experience with a light
and highly agile build.</text>
<text id="53030000">Mass-produced bipedal leg parts developed by Arquebus.
A number of refinements and updates have been made to the
strong foundation laid by the preceding model, creating a
masterpiece in the realm of second-generation AC parts.</text>
<text id="53040000">Heavyweight bipedal leg parts designed by Arquebus ADD.
Incorporates cutting-edge technology to enable defiance of
the PCA. This model utilizes hover movement for increased
loading capacity and greatly improved stability.</text>
<text id="53050000">Bipedal legs developed by ALLMIND for model ACs. Designed
as part of a research project to extend human sensory
capabilities, with numerous optimizations to create an AC
that, to the pilot, feels like an extension of the body.</text>
<text id="53060000">Lightweight bipedal leg parts developed by Elcano. In
keeping with Elcano's roots in producing and forging
steel, this model exhibits craftsman-like flair, being
light yet retaining high load capacity.</text>
<text id="53070200">Bipedal legs developed by BAWS for an old-generation AC.
Said AC was one of the earliest models, developed to
succeed MT-class machines, and modern fans of such
classic hardware are fond of its characteristic bulk.</text>
<text id="53070300">Bipedal leg parts for construction ACs developed by RaD.
Specced for demolition work, this model makes up for
combat performance shortcomings with its sturdiness
and outstanding loading capacity.</text>
<text id="53070400">Bipedal legs for scout ACs developed by RaD. Originally
specced for surface surveys of astronomical objects, this
model makes up for what it lacks in combat performance
with a light energy footprint and commendable ease of use.</text>
<text id="53080000">Bipedal legs for the HAL 826 piloted AC, developed long
ago by the Rubicon Research Institute. The last of the
Ibis Series and the only piloted Ibis craft, it was built
to be the final safety valve to prevent a Coral Collapse.</text>
<text id="53080100">Bipedal legs for EPHEMERA unpiloted ACs, developed long
ago by the Rubicon Research Institute. An old development
quirk allows for piloted operation, albeit with actuation
translation that outstrips the capability of human nerves.</text>
<text id="53080200">New bipedal leg parts developed by Elcano. This model
utilizes technological insights derived from analyzing
Schneider ACs to achieve improved overall balance and
high suitability for aerial combat.</text>
<text id="53120000">Lightweight reverse-joint legs developed by Schneider.
These legs sacrifice stability and defensive performance
to provide exceptional jumping performance, enabling agile
transitions to aerial combat—as is Schneider's forte.</text>
<text id="53150000">Alternative reverse-joint legs developed by ALLMIND.
Marking a new approach, this part explores changes in
human sensory perception through introduction of alien
elements; in this case, animal-like digitigrade legs.</text>
<text id="53170400">Heavyweight reverse-joint legs for scout ACs developed by
RaD. Originally specced for resource transportation rather
than combat, these legs are capable of leaping up to high
positions while supporting a significant weight burden.</text>
<text id="53200000">Tetrapod leg option developed by Balam. The design
division was all but held at gunpoint to produce a model
that satisfied the Redguns' demand for a highly mobile
AC platform also capable of supporting heavy weaponry.</text>
<text id="53230000">Tetrapod leg parts developed by Arquebus, derived from
an existing model. Intended for tetrapods deployed along-
side Arquebus's bipedal and reverse-joint ACs, this model
focuses on mobility to enable hovering-based fire support.</text>
<text id="53300000">Heavyweight tank parts developed by Balam.
Designed with the simple goal of turning ACs into tanks
capable of carrying the heavy weaponry manufactured
by Dafeng Core Industries.</text>
<text id="53340000">Special tank parts designed by Arquebus ADD.
Prioritizes hovering performance and forward propulsion
to focus on aerial combat. During development, the specs
were stolen and leaked by an independent mercenary.</text>
<text id="53360000">Lightweight tank parts developed by Elcano. Inspired by
wheelchairs made for competitive sports, this product was
an instant success with soldiers who had lost the use of
their legs in combat but still pined for the battlefield.</text>
<text id="53900000">Junk. Originally bipedal leg parts for an old-generation
AC developed by BAWS. RaD engineers infiltrated Institute
City to make field repairs—just enough to make this part
operable, but not enough to fix its weathered armor.</text>
</entries>
</fmg>